warez-host.com 2011-11-01

# Warez-Host.Com - Privacy Policy - Offshore Hosting Services

The Privacy policy below describes how Warez-Host.Com ([International Widespread Services Ltd](http://iws.co/)) collects and uses information about its customers and website visitors (The Users)  

**What information is collected from the User by the Company?**

Different types of personally identifiable information are collected from the user by the Company in order for the company to be able to provide its services. These includes, but is not limited to: name, mailing address, telephone numbers, email addresses, credit card information and other information that may be needed for providing the services requested by the User. All this information is provided voluntarily by the User through various order forms, email messages sent to the Company, submit forms, identification forms of LiveChat, information provided by the telephone etc.

The Company also collects different types of non-personally identifiable information about its website visitors. These include but are not limited to referral URL's, Users' IP addresses, Users' use of website, information about the browsers used by the User, etc. Some of this information is collected through Cookies, which are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and are stored on your computer's hard drive and help the Company identify the User. The user has the choice to modify his/her browser and thus to reject the Company's cookies.

**How does the Company use the collected User's information?**

The company uses the collected User's information mainly to provide the service requested by the User. It is used for initial service provision and ongoing User's support. The information can also be used by the Company for sending periodic emails announcing important service changes, new features, technical issue updates and news, different promotions etc. The Users may decide NOT to receive such emails by replying to any of them with "Unsubscribe" in the subject. The information is also used for improving the Company's effectiveness. Based on the data collected the company tries to improve its advertising and sales efforts, website layout and content and to make the overall experience of the User more rewarding. The information can also be used for resolving ownership and other disputes and enforcing agreements between the Company and the User.

**Does the company disclose User's information to third parties?**

The Company may disclose the Users' personal information to its business partners, independent contractors or other third parties together with whom the Company provides its services. For example: the Credit card information of the User may be provided to the card issuing bank, or other partnering entity involved in the payment processing for payment confirmation and verification; the personal information of anyone, who uses the domain name registration services of the Company, is available in the public WHOIS searches as required by the domain name registration regulations; User's personal and business related information may be provide to the SSL certificate provider with whom the Company cooperates for providing the SSL certificate service to the User, etc. The use of the data provided by the Company to these partnering service providers is governed by their own Privacy Policies and is beyond the Company's control.

The Company may also disclose the User's personal information if this is required by law, or the Company believes in good faith that it has to do so to protect the rights and the property of Company or its customers.

The Company may also transfer personal information of its Users in connection with a sale of the Company's business.

**What is done by the Company to prevent loss, misuse or alteration of the User's information?**

The company guarantees that it applies strictly all the industry standard security measures to protect the personal information collected from its users. These include but are not limited to: password protected access to the personal information, limited access to the sensitive data, encrypted transfer of sensitive data submitted by the User through the Company's order forms, login forms etc. However, there may be security and privacy limitations which are beyond the Company's control. By choosing to provide personal information to the Company the user understands and agrees that the security, integrity and privacy of his/her information cannot be 100% guaranteed. 

The company reserves the right to change the above Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes will become effective and binding after their posting on Warez-Host.Com website. The user agrees to regularly review this privacy policy and be aware of the changes made. By continuing to use the Company's services and website after any posted revision, the User agrees to abide by it.

To report an incidence of abuse, please report it to abuse@warez-host.com

**Last Updated:** December 11, 2009
